Guide to the WCSU Office of University Publications & Design Records RG 7.3.2 RG 7.3.2
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Photographs
  - University Photographer's photo archive
    - Prints - Feb 2002-Mar 2002 (Box psa_20)
      Contents: Lorraine Copabianco; Tastebud; science horizons; a day of caring; Barbara Grossman; Nature Preserve-Rain; football banquet; Jason Davis; minority recognition; Barbara Barnwell; Artwork; Don McCabe; Jack Mario; Old Main; Woodwind quartet; O'Neil Center; read across america; AACSB reception; holistic Dr. Judith; orchestra jimenez;; Number of photo packages: 18
    - Prints - Mar 2002 (Box psa_21)
      Contents: Westside; downtown; Jeff Wiggins; artistic process panel; nursing career fair; softball breakfast; Bill Curry; Dave Horowitz; Darla Shaw; Young Library; WCSU signage; executive forum; jazz combos; children's day; danbury hospital; Rich Sullivan; weather day; Afghanistan photographer; tea ceremony; nature preserve; night shots Bear Mountain; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Apr 2002 (Box psa_22)
      Contents: Connie Wilds; Ron Drozdenko; Jim Maloney; Ruth Guyere; Accepted students day; silo; Jean Houston's holistic; Magic Flute; Art alum forum; Bill joel; Irene Sherlock at Haas; Mark Hussey; I want My MTV; campus kids; police car; tennis; Waterbury; Career Fair; Audry Flack; Weir Farm; Connie Evans; Number of photo packages: 17
    - Prints - Apr 2002 (Box psa_23)
      Contents: Nursing sigma theta tau; nemzer symposium; connie wilds retirement; percussion day music; Barnard Awards; westside sculpture collapse; Herb Janick; Roger Kastel; foundation dinner; westside at night; Russell Hirshfeld; River Bend clean up; sigma chi miracle network; nursing; midtown; earth day; Gillian Martin Sorenson; Number of photo packages: 20
    - Prints - Apr 2002-May 2002 (Box psa_24)
      Contents: College academic day at Hartford; center for collaboration; Dr. Bernstein; arbor day; oak tree dedication; faculty recognition; secretary's breakfast; Janet fish-weir; jazzfest; Dr. Labriola; cheerleaders; derby day; men's tennis; softball; education psychology fair; jump-a-thon; Israel/Palestinian Conflict; Jane Goodall; student leadership; computer room westside; cashier's office; illustration show; golf tournament;; Number of photo packages: 24
    - Prints - May 2002 (Box psa_25)
      Contents: Computer rooms; student formal; legislative breakfast; university ball; english grad readings; graphics portfolio; MFA show; west cafe barbeque; Dr. Roach with polish guests; professional studies awards; baseball; employee of the year; ancel graduate reception; new women's basketball coach; rocking chair; Dr. Jannick; dunkin donuts; Number of photo packages: 16
    - Prints - May 2002-Jun 2002 (Box psa_26)
      Contents: Aerial photos (2 packages removed by Peggy Stewart, 8/1/2017); student tech center; dunkin donuts; graduation; John Devine; marketing certificates; Warner and Haas; Higgins roof; Dr. Dever; Helena Sasso; retirement dinner; alumni picnic; university hall roof; western wear; Helen Barksdale; police dept. swearing in; Newbury Hall; Litchfield Hall; student center; old main; grasso hall; pinney hall; classroom building; midtown buildings; Jody's dinner; Dr. Owoye; Bulls bridge; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Jul 2002-Aug 2002 (Box psa_27)
      Contents: string camp; Concap; westside stadium; EAP presentation; Silo Artists; psychology dept.; Herb Janick; Great hollow; new faculty; Rob Eisenson; Dave Brubeck; midtown; westside; baseball camp; Mark Boughton; Frank Dye; Ellen Durnin; Margaret Cicalese; Carol Hawkes; Arlene Krenik; Library art installation; MFA students; alumni office; freshman orientation; faculty picnic; nursing; Number of photo packages: 25
    - Prints - Sep 2002 (Box psa_28)
      Contents: Midtown; Boyer at Library; Macricostas; photronics; taste of Danbury; postcards at Haas Library; Club Carnival on quad; bagpipes; Danbury fire dept. at WCSU; Rich Sullivan; midtown bridge; polish banner; Dr. Mel; Goble, Isaacs, and Jimenez music; Mark Boughton political science class; grad. student reception; 9/11 march; Genny Innes; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Sep 2002-Oct 2002 (Box psa_29)
      Contents: Centennial; volleyball; MTV on campus; James Roach; German students; faces of WestConn; Men's soccer; silent witness; National Council of Jewish Women; westside construction; Board of Trustees; Cabaret; golden circle; Number of photo packages: 13
    - Prints - Oct 2002 (Box psa_30)
      Contents: Football; women's soccer; Billy Collins; Volleyball; Rona Gurkewitz; Jan Alexander; CELT; Darla Shaw; War with Iraq; James Earl Jones; football; homecoming; Andy Rogers; Art drawing class; William Kasbarian; El Salvador; Senator Jepsen; Arts and Science time capsule; Danbury garden club civic award; James Rowland; Tom DaLuca; Number of photo packages: 18
    - Prints - Oct 2002-Nov 2002 (Box psa_31)
      Contents: Football; Steve the Janitor; Athletic Hall of Fame; homecoming; spooky reading; Waterbury reunion; MFA lecture; Halloween; Renovation of Old Main; NECTOP; Oktoberfest; Jazz; fireplace in Fairfield; admissions open house; employee recognition Peggy Stewart; 5k runners; Meet Me in St. Louis;; Number of photo packages: 18
    - Prints - Nov 2002 (Box psa_32)
      Contents: Dinner Theater; effects of war; art bus trip; wine tasting; salute to vets; frisbee in front of fairfield; cat's meow; Bob Alberetti mural; women's basketball; Newman Center; psychology faculty; school of professional studies alumni; westconn society; Bob Berg jazz; football; alumni theater; men's basketball; freshman meeting; sportsmanship summit; George Selleck; Darla Shaw Minority Conference; Number of photo packages: 20
    - Prints - Dec 2002 (Box psa_33)
      Contents: Waterbury; CTA one acts; Dan Joynt; child abuse conference; midtown snow; women's basketball; music dept.; MFA McGarrell; James Roach; Dr. Hogan; Human Rights at the mall; art advanced figure drawing; human rights day; rose caoli and mall; flutes at children's center; women's alumni basketball; holiday jazz; Melissa Lahoud; Moscow ballet; westside Ives; coffee please; John Hurbon; Ronnie Hendrix; Roy and Ginny Young award; Number of photo packages: 17
    - Prints - Jan 2003-Feb 2003 (Box psa_34)
      Contents: Westside snow; Mary F; macricostas reception; men's basketball; women's basketball; super breakfast; costco; Tom Daley; Women's swim team; Sesame Street; O'Neill center; Biology dept.; Cynn Chadwick; Cheryl Beck; study group in library; student protests; Number of photo packages: 14
    - Prints - Feb 2003-Mar 2003 (Box psa_35)
      Contents: Centennial campaign kick-off; blizzard of 2003; midtown snow; circus at O'Neill; women's basketball; men's basketball; Roberts Avenue; read across america; adjunct breakfast; arithmos meeting; Sarah Griswold; Jane Goodall reception; Brad Garner - flute; costco decorating cakes; shelter rock school; alumni party at warner; smithsonian signing Boehringer Ingelheim at student center; Danbury hospital; city hall; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Mar 2003-May 2003 (Box psa_36)
      Contents: Winter warm-up; Children's Day at Danbury High School; Dr. Machell and bagpipes; Westside nature preserve; bagpipes fishbowl; CMEA concert; music dept.; Waterbury nurse tea; career fair; alcohol awareness day; Barnard Awards; guiding lights; jazzfest; art show; baseball; 5k run; education dept.; roots and shoots; student leadership; miscellaneous campus shots; puzzle pieces; Number of photo packages: 19
    - Prints - Jun 2003-May 2004, 2003-2004 (Box psa_37)
      Contents: westside campus; midtown campus; alumni picnic; resident life - camp sloane; freshmen weekend; Jean Glasscock; horses; kids on campus; football; homecoming; football - senior day; nature preserve; alumni dinner theater; women in Afghanistan; Sheka Lawakili; football banquet; career fair; graduation gym; Ben Connito; Francine D'Emico; Eyewitness reliability lecture; effects of war; kids in library; faculty breakfast; graduation; Number of photo packages: 23
    - Prints - 1990-2003 (Box psa_38)
      Contents: Macricostas, Roach, Feldman, Africa trip, includes CDs, many dups; Number of photo packages: 10+
    - CDs - undated (Box psa_39)
      Contains: 37 evelopes,plus large photos not in envelopes. Topics: WXCI; Gerkowicz; Fairfield Hall; West Side Campus; Bill Hawkins; Walter Bernstein; Football; Spirit Band; Tailgating; Annual Report; Earth Day; Violence against women; cancer fair; wine tasting; Wagner Erman; Roach; Rowland; Skitch Henderson; faculty breakfast; Phyllis Ross; Kathleen Deschenes; Fred Hammond; Sue Thomas; Sigma Theta Tau induction; University Awards; Campus Shots; Dorms; Kids; Tony; Homecoming 2001; John Wallace; Cabaret; O'Neill Center; Centenial Scholarship; Faces of WestConn; WestConn Remembers; 9/11 2002; Homecoming; Oak Tree dedication; Viewbook shots 2003; Choral rehearsal; marketing; CTA food
    - CDs - Dec 2002-Apr 2003 (Box psa_40)
      Contains: 92 envelopes. Topics: garden club; painting/illustration show; Centennial ball; Melrose School visit; Tom Philbrick: Brazil Rainforest Presentation; Concert Choir; Jason's Music Camp; Golf Scramble; Campus to Campus; Honors Conference; Jazz Fest; German Studies; foundation board dinner; Ramada Inn; Guiding Lights Education Program; Social work senior project; green knoll day camp; Senior portfolio; Jet Blue; David Neeleman; Women's softball; senior day; women's lacrosse; PAC; IAC; Campus candids; nursing student award; president to president scholarship; West Side new stadium; PE Class walking trails; Barnard awards; MFA Lecture series; Yvonne Jacquette; Easter Egg Hunt; Olympics; Dean's lecture series; HMS Pinafore; Alchohol Awareness Day; Computer animation; career fair; ALS Awareness; Art Alum forum; Emeriti luncheon; Quit smoking; social work department; Baseball; design award; Waterbury campus; ceramics; manhattan string quartet; Joan Macko; Dr. Dubiel; "Tug of war"; Dave Ruffel; Sybil Ludington; Founder's Hall; "Getting in and out of Iraq"; Wild Winter Warmup; Grimes; Centennial Ball Committee; Jamie-Lynn Sigler; News-Times Birthday; Jane Goodall Roots and Shoots; 100th birthday; Basketball; L.E.C. Tourney; Cheerleaders; Meteorology; Ed Club; Clubs Carnival; Iraq Conflict; AIDS Awareness; Frank Herbert; Chinese New Year; African Film Festival; NBC Today Show; Ice Hockey; PSNYC Class; Dr Hines "Everyday Chemistry"; Macricostas; Tray Riding; Old Main
    - CDs - May 2003-May 2003 (Box psa_41)
      Contains: 46 envelopes. Topics: IA Campaign Cocktail party; Campus police department; medal of valor; board of government; Sybil and Friends; retirement; education department; Ives Center cocktail party; Dave Machell's Dinner; Graduation; Commencement; Paddle Day; Fairfield Hall; Midtown Campus; Athletics-- Senior Banquet; registrar's office; Spagetti Eddie/ Ryan San Angeleo; Dave Heneberry Marketing Certificate; Fitness @ City Hall; Holistic Fair; West side Nature Preserve / Garden; JLA Softball Game; Psychology Day; Centennial WestCafe; College Day @ Capital; Honors program; alumni band; Robert D'angelo; The Jumpathon; Grahpic Design Show; Ancell School; Centennial Ball; Project Freedom; MFA Advisory Board; Student Leadership Banquet; Earth Day; Softball Tournament; Campers at Litchfield Hall; Esther Boriss
    - CDs - Jun 2003-Sep 2003 (Box psa_42)
      Contains: 100 envelopes. Topics: Rob Wittemore; Global Access Project; Football, W. Patterson; Darla Shaw; Banned Books; Steve Williams-Mars; Midtown; German visitors; Mark Twain; Olivia Twain; Science Building; Warner Hall; Red house demolition; Grad studies reception; Tulips; Danbury Library Plaza - Ground-breaking; CTA; Nursing Lab; Carina Bandhaver; Dr. Buccini; Biology (outdoor class); Spacesuit- West Side Observatory; UN Doves; Football game vs Salva Regina; Jane Goodall; Centennial Grove; Masks; Laura Barnes Weldon; Bill Hawkins; Dr. Roach; second anniversary of 9/11; Iraq war; scholarship baby; women's volleyball; O'Neill center; alumni news; cabaret; football scrimmage; orientation; Konover; A&S Faculty; Mars night; SPS welcome back; new faculty headshots; west side nature preserve; media services; ATMI donation; hall of fame; James Joyce; Centennial memorial concert; alumni board; Berkshire Gym; meteorology; EAP graduation; Counselling internship; UC Tech classrooms; White Hall; CTA 'butterflies and dragons'; stadium; cultural day; conncap/upward bound; West Side stadium; Old Main; Haas; Warner Hall; Observatory; Pinney; Archives; Howard Tuvelle; Golf at Watertown; Grasso Dorm; Hawley Dorm; Litchfield Dorm; CTA Communications class; history project; blue banners
    - CDs - Oct 2003-Dec 2003 (Box psa_43)
      Contains: 92 envelopes. Topics: Haas; Cupola; Holocaust speaker; nursing tea; alumni board holiday dinner; education students - human rights @ the mall; Bruce Shapiro & Scott Harris; Opera dress rehearsal - Amalah; Pegolotta; Math & Science education students; swimming; jazz combo masterclass; "Kiss Me Kate"; International week; Senate meeting; centennial campaign; wine tasting; Alumni awards; university relations; food workers protest; presidents search; Salute to Veterans; Nick Bellantoni; Western Connection; German Studies; Danbury Hospital: Strook Tower; Patriot Act; Homecoming; WestConn Society Lunch; Women's basketball; psychology department; observatory; mock crash; time capsule ceremony; scholarship baby; IA Alumi Phonathon; Homecoming; Todd Brewster: Civil Liberties; Chemistry Club; EGMC Conference; Nursing dinner; NCAA week; faculty-student basketball; ultimate Frisbee; mock trial; street fair; alumni tent; athletic hall of fame; alumni circle; cabaret; alumni art show; women's health fair; wine tasting; women's soccer; university relations; library plaza renovation; science building construction; East Lake; Marcia Wallace: evening of light and laughter; Brookfield LIbrary; Football; Retirement; Golden Circle Luncheon; Wesley Ball Music Library; Bot Luncheon; Men's soccer
    - CDs - Jan 2004-Apr 2004 (Box psa_44)
      Contains: 99 envelopes. Topics: Stadium canopy; Alcohol & Drug; Women's basketball alumni game; snow; center for collaboration; emotional intelligence; admissions; class of 1993; basketball (women and men's); men's ice hockey; Big Band Jazz; Health fair; global access project; Branson donation; political science; CTA; Rotary club; undergrad application; senior day; nursing career fair; stadium progress; WestConnWare; "Twelth Night"; women's softball; westerners art auction; peer leadership group; firefighter honors; capital campaign cocktail party; senate meeting and debate team; nursing scholar program; community coalition lunch; social work seniors; WestConn Nature preserve; WNP; Future Teachers conference; university relations group; softball; read across america; alumni dinner theater; Danbury Hospital Children's day; Danbury City Hall; Diverse roles of women; capital day; President Lecture Series; Emeriti Luncheon; Alchohol Awareness Day; Men's lacrosse; Men's tennis; Haas Award; Career Fair; 5th Art Forum; "Street Scenes" (opera); women's lacrosse; science night; "Broadway and 42nd"; Jazz Fest; Roach Retirement; Rwanda; Anifest; Cyber Security award; SGA; Concert choir; Barnard Awards; Senior portfolio; Graphic Design; Illustration; Photography; Painting; Poverty Day
    - CDs - May 2004-Jul 2004 (Box psa_45)
      Contains: 91 envelopes. Topics: Spring explosion concert; Dr. Roach Retirement; MFA board meeting; SLB; jumpathon; education connection; professional studies; athletics senior banquet; Ancell School Honors convention; drama class; ACA Advisement open house; school of arts and science honors convocation; ball at Southbury Hilton; CT Honors Conference; Holistic Health fair; Jazz Fest Clinics; Media awards; student concert at Ives; Sousa Dinner; Graduate students reception; Centennial Grove; CTA; Roots and Shoots; Dance Team 10th anniversary performance; Goodall Dinner; Ives Center; Spring Carnival; Cheerleaders Car Wash; Wedding; NYC Picasso; Foundation Dinner; Police Inspection; Graduation; Commencement; Orientation; President to President Scholarship; South Street School; CEO Forum; WestCafe; James R. Roach Library Recognition Award; Science Night at Candlewood Lake; Danbury Library Ribbon Cutting; Armory; Newtown Savings Bank; West Side Dorm construction; media association; alumni picnic; bookstore; rotary scholarship luncheon; alumni circle plaque; counseling center; Haas Library Stacks Marsha Daria; Excel program at the Acadamic Center for Excellence; Bike Sunday; German Students visit city hall; Kabuki; Trash American Style: Malcolm; Golf Outing; Alumni golf; Candlewood Lake Project
    - CDs - Jul 2004-Sep 2004 (Box psa_46)
      Contains: 82 envelopes. Topics: Speedy pizza; "goodbye Roach"; Great Hollow; Smart Art; science building, alumni babies; music camp; excel program; SPS faculty meeting; school of professional studies; disability services; O'Neill center; football; rooftop shots; WestConnect; "Voices" performance; Alumni Circle medallion; Schmotter's First Day; Class of 1954 reunion; star party; laser tag; MFA writing for AR; Men's soccer; Colonial Football; Dance class on quad; Fossil Fuel debate; Football vs. Rowan; Get out the Vote; Counselling center; Women's tennis; Pathways Nursing; Fisheye Trials; holistic panel; centennial hall; pizza with the president; Hawkins; Inherit the Wind; Banned Books week; David Faber: Holocaust; Honors seminar; Jazz ensemble; Choices forum; Childcare benefit performance; German Scholars visit; non-traditional group
    - CDs - Sep 2004-Oct 2004 (Box psa_47)
      Contains: 30 envelopes, 30 CDs envelopes. Topics: buildings, Danbury library, Central African Republic seminar, NCAA baskeball, Christmas decoration, Crosby Street Fire, students, football, volleyball, Dr. Roach, Greeks; Thurman, NY; Danbury High School; Alcohol Awareness; African Film Festival; String instruments; social work conference; music camp; flute camp; Logos; Seals; marketing images; psychologogy conference; DHS reunion; Cabaret; music department; salute to vets; orientation;dorm photos; homecoming 2001
    - CDs - Oct 2004-Nov 2004 (Box psa_48)
      Contains: 64 envelopes. Topics: Oscar delos Santos talk; Danbury Pearl Day; football; cheerleaders; spirit band; science at night; Ability Beyond; Higgins; Board of Trustees meeting; health fair; scholarship reception; local candidates debate; women's volleyball; badminton; women's basketball; women's soccer; alumni luncheon; golden circle; Halloween; Hord Foundation; Ice hockey; octoberfest; jazz; appellate court; Judge West's reception;social work honor society; "Threats and Promises" political panel; dorm dedication; homecoming; street fair; mascot; dance team; homecoming king and queen; alumni awards; class of 1964 reunion; class of 1959 reunion; athletic hall of fame; alumni circle rededication; tailgating; pizza with the president; alumni art show; governor's service award; Chemistry Wizards; training for campus police; Spanish class; NCAAW Sex and Candy; classes; NCAAW Athletes Day; Westside Nature Preserve blue trail; Ives celebration; Veterans event; rugby; alumni dinner; MCCA award; Chemistry club; donors; Japanese tea ceremony; time management lecture; Dr. Steffan; international week; Filipino dancing; Newman Center; operation christmas packages; Thanksgiving dinner; cloning: Frank Dye; graduate students; classical and folk dances of the middle east; wine tasting; ice cream making in chemistry class; Dean's inaugural meeting; shelter of the cross; symphonic wind orchestra; \
    - CDs - Nov 2004-Dec 2004 (Box psa_49)
      Contains: 26 envelopes. Topics: Edwin Drood production; Holiday Show; Salvation Army; percussion ensemble; orchestra; choir performance; auditions for Edwin Drood; West Side Dorm ribbon cutting; women's basketball; President's holiday party for community; pizza with the president; debate team; executive forum; alumni circle medallion; "One Acts" dress rehearsals; Hord Academy; "Sew What" group; "Amahl" dress rehearsal; jazz masterclass; emeriti luncheon; alumni holiday dinner; HPX; Future Teachers and Education Club; Drood Cast Party; Shelter of the cross
    - CDs - Jan 2005-Apr 2005 (Box psa_50)
      Contains: 73 envelopes. Topics: Cabaret; career fair; fly me to the moon; senior project; meteorology; roots and shoots; freedom live; westerners art auction; O'Neill center; employee recognition; bagpipes; St. Baldrick's Day; Vagina Monologues; body imaging; German studies; Social Work department meeting; nursing; OWHE conference; NCAA; valves and vision; ergonomics; men's basketball; snow; women's basketball; spirit band; minority teacher recruitment; "the distance from here"; ConnCap; Hord Academy; RAD training; self-defense; sounds of africa; Women's swimming; President's community reception; Dean Walter Kramer; african film festival; tsunami relief; football banquet; institutional advancement; career development; student life; admissions; WestConn society lunch; MFA writing; Doing Business with Brazil; Jaime Melo; MLK celebration; Winchester donation; class of 1960 reunion
    - CDs - Jan 2005-May 2005 (Box psa_51)
      Contains: (large) 14 envelopes. Topics: commencement; blue window NYC; inauguration; James Schmotter; WWE at the O'Neille Center; values and vision; stakeholders meeting; Wild Winter Warmup; Men's basketball; ice hockey; "Colored Girls"; scholastic project; Dana Shaw
    - CDs - Jul 2005-Sep 2005 (Box psa_53)
      Contains: 58 envelopes. Topics: combatting sex slavery; OWLs (non-traditional students); banned books; science building ribbon cutting; men's soccer; leukemia/lymphoma walk; light up the night; women's basketball; shoes for nine; manhattan string quartet; NSCS canned food drive for Huriccane Katrina; Smithsonian rare books event; women's tennis; constitution day; MFA lecture; football; Americares donation drive; choices: tiki party on quad; NFFIS; Ives concert park; softball; women's soccer; women's field hockey; freshman day; bridge the gap (math); president's picnic; RA/RD training; peer education: choices; DMHS Vault; nursing reception; summer literary festival; ConnCap; artistic shots of feet; IL organ purchase committee; jazz/band camp; summer flowers; pizza with the president; string camp; cycle Sunday at the O'Neill center; German students; class of 1948; girls' basketball camp
    - CDs - Apr 2005-Dec 2005 (Box psa_54)
      Contains: 22 envelopes. Topics: band/jazz camp; alumni circle; Twelfth Night; freshman day; gate ceremony and address; alumni laundry bags; women's soccer; West Side Student Center construction; Ives Concert Park; Americares; Choices barbecue; 9/11 Memorial; Sandip Burman & Friends dancing; men's soccer; combating sex slavery; banned books; MFA lecture; Bill Clinton visit; Chinese culture classes; homecoming; alumni tailgating; homecoming; 1955 reunion; 1960 reunion; 1975 reunion; ice hockey; Nine dress rehearsal; American Vietnamese History; Dr. Keith Taylor from Cornell
    - CDs - Oct 2005-Dec 2005 (Box psa_55)